hi everyone this is Joe Brewer just
wanted to send us quick note by video to
say I'm really excited to be part of the
regenerative communities Network and
what I'm really hoping to do with all of
you in the next months and years is to
help create a proper ecosystem of
learning between the different
regenerative field sites and projects
that are joining this community as many
of you are well aware the website that
we're using is really just a convening
place for creating tools sharing
knowledge and resources posting events
helping to exchange money or to provide
opportunities for employment or
volunteering and things like this which
you'll learn more about as we go along
but more important than the website are
the actual sites physically in the
ground at different locations around the
world so this is one of the big things
about this network that we want to
really do as much what as we possibly
can as I don't need to really push on or
make any more emphasis on the urgency of
the global crisis that we're in just
want to say that what's really inspiring
about this network is the way that we
are focusing our selves on increasing
the biodiversity of physical places of
restoring ecological functions where
landscapes have been degraded and
increasing the health and resilience of
communities where they're going to
seriously need it in the future and also
to inspire and demonstrate what
regenerative economic principles look
like in practice so I'm very excited to
be joining you and playing the role that
I have is the capacity cultivator to
help build all of our capacities to do
this work at each location around the
world and so that we form a proper
network of collaboration between those
projects so let me know if you have any
questions if you want to schedule a time
to talk and
let's get to work making this network as
vibrant and impactful as we possibly can